<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homes on David Shih</title>
    <link>https://davidshih175.github.io/home/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Homes on David Shih</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://davidshih175.github.io/home/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://davidshih175.github.io/home/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://davidshih175.github.io/home/about/</guid>
      <description>Biography I was a Process Analysis Engineer at Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Company (TSMC). I have solid experience in data analysis and software development for semiconductor process design and control.
Now I’m currently a Software Engineer Intern at AYC Group LLC and focus on Web development as well as software design.
Resume</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experience</title>
      <link>https://davidshih175.github.io/home/work-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://davidshih175.github.io/home/work-experience/</guid>
      <description>AYC Group LLC Dallas, TX, United States Software Engineer InternMay 2018-Jan 2019 Analyzed sales orders, purchase orders, revenue and customer behavior data to build a sales forecasting model using Python and sklearn library, improving the accuracy rate of procurement by more than 93%. Integrated SOAP/REST APIs of UPS, ChannelAdvisor, Bigcommerce and Fishbowl to migrate data from inventory systems to marketplace applications, enhancing the efficiency of operator by 85% and reducing 90% human errors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://davidshih175.github.io/home/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://davidshih175.github.io/home/projects/</guid>
      <description>House Prices: Advanced Regression Techniques Technology: Python | kaggle
 Implemented normalization, evaluation and visualization for raw data, fine-tuned parameters of classifiers. Reduced redundant features and optimized algorithms, decreasing mean squared error by 20%.

Implement a simple video processing application in LITMUSRTLink Technology: C | Linux | FFmpeg
 Applied LITMUSRT to evaluate the performance of real-time scheduling (PSN-EDF, P-FP, C-EDF and GSN-EDF). Implemented simple video as an input source, designed C program to link FFmpeg and LITMUSRT for decoding.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publication</title>
      <link>https://davidshih175.github.io/home/publication/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://davidshih175.github.io/home/publication/</guid>
      <description>The Study of Fabrication and Tribological Properties of Rubber Based Friction MaterialLink Advised by Prof. Chien-Ping Ju, Master Thesis, NCKU, Jul 2012
 Investigated the effects of diverse fabrication parameters (heating rate of post-cured、molding pressure、temperature of post-cured and molding temperature) on tribological properties of Nitrile Butadiene Rubber (NBR)-based friction material. The mechanical properties, tribological properties, and microstructure of NBR based friction material are measured by Shore-type hardness tester, sliding wear tester, surface roughness tester and scanning electron microscopy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://davidshih175.github.io/home/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://davidshih175.github.io/home/contact/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>